skyparksecure.com 2019-06-22

# SkyParkSecure - Privacy Policy - We take your privacy seriously

## **Privacy policy**

**This Privacy and Cookie Policy was last updated on 14th March 2019.**

**1.  Data Controller**

**SkyParkSecure**.com is a trading name of SkyParkSecure Limited. SkyParkSecure Limited is part of the Manchester Airport Group Plc.

The data controller is SkyParkSecure Limited registered in England and Wales registered number 5602720. In this Privacy Policy, ‘we’,’ us’ and ‘our’ means SkyParkSecure Limited. Where data is provided to our partners in relation to the service you have requested, our partners may also be acting as data controllers. If you would like more information about how any of our partners process data, you should read the privacy policy for the relevant partner which will be available on the partner’s website.

At SkyParkSecure, safeguarding your personal information and handling your information in a compliant way is important to us. We understand and respect the importance of guarding your privacy and are committed to protecting your personal information.

The processing of your information is to facilitate your purchase and to communicate future discounts when opted into receiving such marketing communication via email.  

**2\. Your rights**

The General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR) gives you certain rights relating to the personal data that is processed by Sky Parks Secure. Find below the list of rights and what they mean. If you wish to exercise any of these rights, please contact our Data Protection Officer at our address below, or alternatively you can send an email to **webmaster@skyparksecure.com**. You will receive an acknowledgement within three working days of sending your request and a full response within twenty-eight days of receiving all the relevant information required to handle your request.

**Right of Access** – You have the right to access all the personal information and supplementary information that we hold about you. This will allow you to be aware of and verify the lawfulness of us processing your information. We would respond to your subject access request within twenty-eight days. Please or contact our Data Protection Officer at the address at the end of this notice, if you wish to make a subject access request.

**Right to Rectify** – You have the right to request for your inaccurate personal information to be rectified or completed if it is incomplete.

**Right to Erasure** – We automatically delete your information from our records when the retention period has lapsed. Prior to us automatically deleting your information, you have the right to request for your information to be deleted and have your personal information erased from our records, if there is no reason for us to hold your information.

**Right to Restrict Processing** \- You have the right to object to the processing of your information if it causes unwarranted and substantial damage or distress. If it does, you have the right to require us to stop (or not to begin) the processing in question. This right does not automatically trigger the right to erasure. You will have to request for your information to be fully deleted from our records if you wish to exercise your right to erasure.

**Right to Data Portability** – You have the right to obtain and reuse your personal information which we hold. This compelling will allow you to move, copy or transfer personal information easily from one IT environment to another in a safe and secure way.

**Right to Object** – You have the right to object to us using your personal information for direct marketing and profiling. This right can be exercised at any point in time, whether at the point where we collect your personal information, or after we already have already collected your personal information. If you want to object to us processing your personal information, please contact the Data Protection Officer at our address at the end of this notice. Alternatively, you can also exercise the right at any time by clicking ‘unsubscribe’ in any marketing email.

**Right to Lodge a Complaint** – You have the right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioner’s Office **[here](https://ico.org.uk/make-a-complaint/)** , if you feel that our processing of your personal information infringes on your rights per the requirements of the General Data Protection Regulation. We advise that you contact our Data Protection Officer at our address at the end of this notice to attempt to resolve it before escalating your complaint to the regulators.

**Right to Withdraw Consent** – You have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. Your withdrawal of consent shall not affect the lawfulness of processing of your data before the withdrawal. You can withdraw consent by contacting our Data Protection Officer at the address below, or alternatively, you can click ‘unsubscribe’ in any marketing email to withdraw consent in relation to marketing

To contact us about any of your rights set out in this Privacy Policy please write to the Data Protection Officer at SkyParkSecure Limited, SkyPark House, 10 Newton Drive, Blackpool, Lancashire, FY3 8B, or email  **[webmaster@skyparksecure.com](mailto:webmaster@skyparksecure.com "Email")**. Please provide your full name, email address, and booking reference when contacting us.

**3\. Providing data about other people**

This privacy policy sets out in detail how your data will be used by us. If you are providing us with another person’s data you should ask them to also read this Privacy Policy. By giving us information about another person you are confirming that they have given you consent to provide the information to us.

**4\. How your personal data will be used**

We collect your personal information to enable us to provide you with our goods and services. This includes, among others, the information you provide when you use our websites and/or our servicesIf you want to view the data collected for your booking, then you can do this by going to ‘MyAccount’

It is very important to us that we provide a service that meets the expectations of our customers and this section will explain how we use your data to communicate with you.

**Booking Confirmation**

When you make a booking through us, you will automatically be sent confirmation of your booking by email or SMS so that you have a record of your booking and can easily retrieve your booking in the future. This is a standard part of the service that we offer and by using the service you agree to receive these communications.

**Updates from SkyParkSecure.com**

Where you tell us you are happy to receive information from us we may send you communications from SkyParkSecure.com which may include the following: -

\- Email Offers   
\- Important pre-travel information about your booking   
\- New product launches   
\- Updates on our rewards programme   
\- Opportunities to participate in market research

If you don’t want to receive marketing communications from us you can let us know at any time by contacting us at **[feedback](https://www.skyparksecure.com/contact-us)** , or you can unsubscribe via the **[update your email preferences](https://www.skyparksecure.com/unsubscribe-choices)**.

**5\. Product / service providers websites**

We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other websites. Whenever possible we will only partner with other websites which maintain the same standards as are present on our own website but we cannot guarantee this. If you click through to any of our product or service providers to their own website, you will be subject to that product or service provider’s website terms and conditions and privacy policy which we would recommend you read carefully.

We always put our customers first!
